[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "How is he feeling on the verge of his big Broadway debut?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "It's the hardest, most fun work you can imagine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Can we get back to talking about me, please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Tonight, they spill his secrets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "Is he a good kisser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "How good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "So-so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "WRB", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How did you find playing a tabloid journalist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, the key about this is that this was when -- forgive me for saying it, but this is when tabloids really mattered.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What does it take, do you think, to be a great actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Studying it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason Robards", "Robert Duvall"]}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Who are the -- who are greatest actors of your lifetime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "The ones that I admire greatly were Jason Robards and Robert Duvall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "She was unfortunately very nice about you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Is there a secret, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I think finding the right person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Do you -- I mean, do you turn it on for your wife, performance-wise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "You mean right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Now those -- those are for the pilot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Can we just -- can you just put on this wrap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "But you know what, we were told, I'm sure you'll recall, the drag element, that's just going to be for the pilot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What is the worst thing you can tell me about Tom Hanks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "He can't hit.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Hanks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Do we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "A demanding diva.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Well, one cop turned to the other one at one point and said hey, hey, Bill, you know who we have here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Have you been surprised by his performances back on a stage like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Not surprised but very -- I have to kind of pull it together because I really do -- I get moved as a friend, not merely as a fellow actor and, you know, we're in early scenes together, suddenly, quickly, there's a lot of courage for any actor, and I don't care who it is, and this guy, he's -- he's tearing --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Nora"]}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Have you contemplated the belly flop in this play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, I will defer to all of Nora's wisdom here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Is it comforting working with four very strong actors?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Dear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "What was that like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well, I had met her briefly, we rehearsed for about a month and then I have decided I wanted to meet her just to meet her without having it affect what we were working on in the room.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How do you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "ORGAN: Is that what she said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "That's sweet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Did you find that difficult?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "No, because I understand -- I understand the desire to be in game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Where's the reward> Where's my badge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "IERNEY: And that's what the story is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Do you ever do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Have any of the views of all of you changed about tabloid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "It hasn't softened my fury.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "But do you -- as some do, do you resent the attention of paparazzi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Or are they part of the business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Part of the business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Is he a good kisser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "How good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "So-so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Did you know, Tom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Not a clue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "What was it about Tom, do you think, that your mother loved so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Well, he's the best.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Are we going to go through them all now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yes, we are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 655, "question": "It was that scene where the -- his older son sits down and asks him, you know, why didn't you like me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "And we shared that because of your scene in \"Fences.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "What did he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "He said you, sir, are a groove.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Nobody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Nobody at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "If I said to you you've got three hours left to live, not that you have, what's the movie you'd make again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "If I had three hours to live, I would not be making a movie, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130321pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "How important is it to you, personally, to be -- and all of you actually to be making what turned out to be Nora's last work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", ":", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "WP", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "I'm just proud to have been -- you know, to have done that reading.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nora"]}}]